Khaled Javedan

Commis chef

United Arab Emirates, Sharjah, Al Suyoh 3 (+98) 050 259 7949 khaledjavedan76@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Persian Kabab, Iran, Hormozgan, Bandar kong—chef

sep 2016 - sep 2017

- Help plan menus, determine the size of food portions, estimating food requirements and costs
- Communicate with suppliers through the ordering and monitoring of supplies
- Marinate and mix ingredients for different kabab recipes.
- Prepared meals for dinner with an average of 100 tables per day
- Prepared all food items according to recipes and menu to ensure the best quality of the products.
- Worked with different kitchen gear including slicer, grill, fryer, stove, oven, blender, meat grinder etc..
- Trained and directed new employees who assisted in preparing and serving meals

Galet Food, Iran, Hormozgan, Bandar kong — *Commis* chef

May 2015 - Sep 2016

- Cooked and prepared food according to special dietary restrictions or number of portions to be served
- Washed pots, pans, dishes, utensils, and other cooking equipment.

EDUCATION

Esfarayen University of technology, iran—Bachelor's degree in computer engineering

Oct 2017 - Sep 2021 GPA: **17.15** of **2**0

SUMMARY

Hardworking cook with 2+ years experience in high volume restaurants excels in multi-tasking and following directions. My knife skills, grace under pressure, and intensive kitchen background ensure that I always put out high-quality plates even during the busiest rushes.

SKILLS

Team work.
Time management.
Team Management & leadership.
great smell & taste skills
Problem Solving.
knowledge of nutrition & Diet.
Technology Skills.
Attention to details

AWARDS

Top Graduate Computer engineer student with average of 17.15 out of 20.

Top Student of the year first year of the college

LANGUAGES

English(fluent) Arabic(native) Farsi(native)